Aldo Kriek

Address: 20 Ulster Crescent Crown Gardens JHB

Phone: +27 822990779 **Email:** noks88@gmail.com

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/aldo-kriek-69760996/

Professional Summary

I consider myself a reliable dedicated person who is self-motivated and willing to go the extra mile to achieve client satisfaction. I believe teamwork is of great importance to achieve goals in the working environment. I enjoy challenges and the ability to learn. 18 years experience in various IT roles such as network administrator, Wireless technician, Onsite and remote customer engineer and site administrator for multiple sites around Gauteng including managing and maintaining the infrastructure for a Telkom college +- (150 -200 users).

Work Experience

03/2019 - 07/2022

Business Connexion (Afrox)

• Tech Officer - IT Customer Engineer

Onsite customer engineer at the clients premises (Afrox) providing onsite technical support for all IT related issues such as Laptop and Desktop repairs, Software and hardware upgrades. Remote support and management of international technicians for neighboring African countries. Deployment of software packages via SCCM and network support LAN/WAN.

09/2017 - 07/2019

Business Connexion (Amadeus)

• IT Site Administrator

Remote and Onsite support administrator for Amadeus clients in the Travel industry. Full site control of clients networks, Data Backups and redundancy, Server support and upgrades. Troubleshooting of Desktop, laptop and All in one devices. Weekly maintenance at client sites. Assisted users remotely via remote tools and helped out with helpdesk calls.

01/2013 - 08/2017

Telkom SA

Senior OPS specialist

Maintained, Managed and ran all IT Computers & networks for 3 main Telkom Sites. (150-200 Users) Desktop & Network Support. Hardware repairs and compliancy verifications on computers. Hardware storeroom manager for Gauteng.

07/2012 - 10/2012

In Touch With The World

• IT Technician

Travelled to various clients and assisted with computer faults and upgrades. Network support and mobile device support. Remote support to clients while assisting users on the helpdesk with SLA calls.

02/2012 - 06/2012

Comtel Communications

• Wireless Network Technician

Installation Of Wireless Satellite network Devices. VOIP & Network Router Support. Ubiquity wireless device installations via microwave technologies and setting up of High site access points. Grand stream VOIP equipment maintenance and installation. Nano station and Pico station installations and configurations

03/2008 - 11/2011

Motata (Telkom SA)

ADSL Technician

Installation Of ISDN, ADSL & telephone Lines while assisting Clients to connect to the internet. Router configurations and Telkom Exchange connections. Internet testing and quality assurance on connections. Wireless setup for clients and VOIP device installations.

Education

01/2019 - 11/2022

Boston Business College

Software Development (Advanced National Diploma NQF6)

Development on front end GUI application while connecting the applications to backend database applications for data storage. Programming Languages such as Java, JavaScript, C#, PHP, SQL). Business management courses such as advanced business management and strategies, Business ethics, Project Management. Linux and Network courses. Cybersecurity courses such as Security + and CEH Ethical hacking while implementing all information into a modern 4th industrial revolution industry.

02/2010 - 11/2011

Boston Business College

• CompTIA N+

Network installation and maintenance via LAN and WAN technologies. Network Security and management via centralized devices. Network terminology such as ARP, DNS, DHCP, IPCONFIG, etc. NAS storage solutions.

02/2007 - 11/2008

Boston Business College

CompTIA A+

Hardware and software troubleshooting. Operating systems and peripheral devices

01/2006 - 11/2007

Boston Business College

Computer Clerk

Microsoft Office and basic computer troubleshooting. Keyboarding and office administration

01/2006 - 11/2007

Boston Business College

Office Assistant

Microsoft Office and basic computer troubleshooting. Keyboarding and office administration

Additional Skills

- Software Development (Front + Backend)
- Programming Languages (Java, Android, C#, HTML)
- Database administration (MySQL & Microsoft Access)
- Agile Methodologies
- CompTIA A+
- · CompTIA N+
- CompTIA Security +
- Ethical Hacking CEH
- Business management
- Business Ethics
- Project Management
- Microsoft Office 365 (2003,2007,2010,2013,2016,2019,2021)
- Microsoft Windows (Win 95, Win 2000, Win XP, Win 7, Win 8.1, Win 10, Win 11)
- · Cloud Solutions & IoT devices.
- Mobile Device Support
- Network Administration
- Active Directory, Windows Server, Domain, SCCM

References

Available upon request